# IRINA DUBROVSKAYA

### **QA ENGINEER**

MINSK · +375 (29) 555-8709 · IRIN.DUBROVSKAYA@GMAIL.COM

I am experienced in creating test documentation, manual tasting and working with testing tools.

I try to find simple solutions to complex tasks. I understand the importance of striking a balance between business goals and user satisfaction. I am sure that success comes only in the right place and with the right people.

# **EXPERIENCE**

## TRAINEE QA ENGINEER

#### INTERNSHIP IN UPSERVICE

- Creating checklists and test cases
- Functional and non-functional testing
- Reporting bugs and improvements
- Creating and monitoring tasks in Jira
- Creating TRR of the team

July 2021 - September 2021

#### PR PRESS-SECRETARY

#### **MTIS**

- SMM
- Creating of requirements for the site
- Coordination of the designer's work, creating simple layouts in Coral Draw
- Planning activities and budget for the year
- Drafting contracts and reporting documentations

September 2016 – December 2022

# **EDUCATION**

### **COURSE BY VADIM KSENDZOV**

"SOFTWARE TESTING"

QA Engineer Minsk

April 2022 - Present

### **COURSE BY IT-ACADEMY**

"SOFTWARE TESTING"

QA Engineer Minsk

July 2021 – September 2021

### **ACADEMY OF PUBLIC ADMINISTRATION**

### HIGHER EDUCATION IN INTERNATIONAL MANAGEMENT AND LAW

Lawyer Minsk

2006 - 2012

# **SKILLS**

#### TOOLS & WORKFLOW

- Creation of test documentation, requirements & TRR
- ✓ All kind of Testing
- Estimation
- ✓ Automation Test Tools: Postman, SoupUI, Selenium IDE (Katalon Recorder)
- ✓ Other Tools: GitHub, TestRail, Jira, Apache JMeter, Virtual Box (Ubuntu), Android Studio, CMD/Terminal, WDC, MySQL Server